recruitmentinfosite.com 2015-04-27

# Privacy Policy ~ Recruitment 2015-16 Notification

In general, you can visit Recruitmentinfosite.com Internet sites without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our Internet servers collect the domain names and ip addresses of visitors and keeps for one month. This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed and similar information.

Recruitmentinfosite.com uses this information to measure the use of our site and to develop ideas to improve the content of our site. We never share your email address with third parties.

 **We Are Committed to Safeguarding Personal Information** In order to better serve your needs now and in the future, we may ask you to provide us with certain information. We understand that you may be concerned about what we will do with such information – particularly any personal information. We agree that you have a right to know how we will utilize the personal information you provide to us. Therefore, we have adopted this Privacy Statement to govern the use and handling of your personal information.  
 **  
Use of Information**  
We request information from you for our own legitimate business purposes and not for the benefit of any non affiliated party. Therefore, we will not release your information to non affiliated parties except: (1) as necessary for us to provide the product or service you have requested of us; (2) as permitted by law; or (3) as otherwise specified herein. Such information may be used for any internal purpose, such as quality control efforts or analysis.

 **Disclaimer**  
Recruitmentinfosite.com provides the content from various information sources ‘as is’ and the content to be used only for informational purpose and not responsible for the inaccuracy or deficiency of the provided information. Recruitmentinfosite.com have the rights, at its sole discretion, to make modifications in any aspect of the provided information.

Recruitmentinfosite.com Internet site may contain links to other Internet sites. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.

 **Cookies**  
This website and some of  Internet sites may make use of “cookie” technology to measure site activity and to customize information to your personal tastes. A cookie is an element of data that an Internet site can send to your browser, which may then store the cookie on your hard drive. The goal of this technology is to better serve you when visiting our site, save you time when you are here and to provide you with a more meaningful and productive Internet site experience.  
 **  
DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.Recruitmentinfosite.com.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.Recruitmentinfosite.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Google DoubleClick & Infolinks.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.Recruitmentinfosite.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.Recruitmentinfosite.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.Recruitmentinfosite.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.  
 **  
Copyright**

If any website wants to link to our articles or quote on it, needs to follow these guidelines.

Use only summary(generally 3 to 5 sentences) from our article and give a link to our article for readers to read full story.You must credit Recruitmentinfosite.com with anchor text/hyperlink pointing to our domain name or article. Never publish full article from our site without our permission.

If you find any copyright issues with  or you wish to print our full articles please contact us at risblogupdate [AT} gmail [DOT] com.
